Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Videotapes, Audiotapes, and Film, 1973-2003; RG0054 Series 38; 17.5 Linear feet (Box 11, Box 9, Box 10, Box 6, Box 7, Box 12, Box 4, Box 8, Box 5, Box 2, Box 1, Box 3, Box 13)
  - Women's Basketball, 01/22/1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Women's Basketball A-10 GW at Rutgers 1/22/95 Tape 1
  - Women's Basketball, 01/22/1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Women's Basketball A-10 GW at Rutgers 1/22/95 Tape 2
  - Women's Basketball, 02/22/1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Debbie Hemery, Darlene Saar WRC-TV 2/22/95
  - Women's Basketball, 02/27/1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Newschannel 8 Debbie Hemery-G.W.U 2/27/95 (Brad Bower) Feb. 24, 1995
  - Women's Basketball, 02/28/1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Channel 55-Women's Basketball Temple vs. G. Washington 2/28/95
  - Women's Basketball, 03/23/1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    GWU Women vs. Colorado 1995 NCAA Tour. Sweet 16 3/23/95 Press Conference
  - Women's Basketball, 03/23/1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    GWU Women vs. Colorado 3/23/95
  - Women's Basketball, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    GW Women 1995 A-10 Final/Penn St./NCAA wins
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    GW Women's Highlights 1995-96
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    95-96 All American Tape Tajama Abraham #40 The George Washington University
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Vesna Perak Women's Basketball '96
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    GW Women's Basketball Noelia Gomez highlights (1998) copy
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    1998 GWU Women's Basketball Team
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    GW Women's B-Ball Hilites 98-99
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    1998-99 George Washington Women's Basketball Highlights
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Noelia Gomez highlight tape 1999 copy
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    The 2000-2001 George Washington University Basketball Highlights Video Women's
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 12/29/2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Rutgers University Women's Basketball vs. GWU 12-29-02
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 12/29/2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    2002-2003 George Washington Women's Basketball Headshots
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Women's Basketball
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    James Brown with Joe Nov. 19
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Movie "The Freshman", GW Women's Basketball, Brad Bower
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    G.W.U. Women's Highlights
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Atlantic 10 Champ. Women's B-ball Rutgers vs. GWU
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    WCB: W-VA @ GWU 2/24/92 and Ch.5 & Ch. 8 Interviews 1992 Volleyball
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    GW Volleyball 1979
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    GW vs. Georgetown Regionals 81
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    GW vs. Georgetown Regionals (Quarter Final) 1981
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Women's Volleyball GW vs. Pitt 1981
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    GW vs. Pitt Regionals 81
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Finals-Pitt 1981 Regionals '81
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    GW vs. Providence Regionals 81-Volleyball
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    GW vs. Providence (bad)
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Rutgers Regionals 81
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Rutgers-Last game Regionals 1981
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    1997 NCAA Women's Volleyball Regular-Season Promotional Message
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    "Keeping Standardized Volleyball Statistics"
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Part I. Volleyball Howard vs. GW
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 02/02/1978 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    2/2/78 7:00 am G.W.U. Women Varsity Swimming Team Title IX Interview with Jim Vance
  - Women's Basketball Volleyball, Swimming, Skeet Trap, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    1990 Intercollegiate Skeet Championships
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/04/1990-12/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hits Dec. 4, 11, 18, 25 1990
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/04/1990-12/25/1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/11/1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Mike Jarvis Show #2 12/11/90
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/29/1990-01/22/1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hits Dec. 29, 1990 Jan. 8, 15, 22 '91
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/29/1990-01/22/1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hits Dec. 29, 1990 Jan. 8, 15, 22 1991
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/08/1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Jarvis Show #6 G.W. Coaches Show 1/8/91
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/29/1991-02/19/1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hits Jan. 29 Feb. 5, 12, 19, 1991
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 02/12/1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Mike Jarvis Show Tape #2 12 Feb. 91
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 02/27/1991-03/22/1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hits Feb. 27, March 5, 12, 22, 1991
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/01/1992-01/03/1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    The Mike Jarvis Show Shows 1, 2, 3 Jan. '92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/07/1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    The Mike Jarvis Show #1 1-7-92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/14/1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    The Mike Jarvis Show #2 1-14-92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/21/1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    The Mike Jarvis Show #3 1-21-92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 02/11/1992-02/18/1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Mike Jarvis Show 11 Feb. 92 18 Feb. 92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 03/10/1992-03/17/1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    The Mike Jarvis Show 10 March 92, 17 March 92
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 11/19/1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    American Cancer Society Coaches vs. Cancer Tags Jarvis 11/19/94
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/16/1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    American Cancer Society "Coaches Versus Cancer" Mike Jarvis 12/16/94
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 12/19/1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    American Cancer Society "Coaches Versus Cancer" Mike Jarvis 12/19/94
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 01/01/1997-01/18/1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    The Mike Jarvis Show 1997 weeks 1 & 3 & 3 Jan 4 & Jan 11 & Jan 18
  - Mike Jarvis Show, 11/11/1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Jarvis Promo Dub 11/11/97
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Mike Jarvis Promo
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Coaches vs. Cancer 1. Mike Jarvis: The George Washington Univ. 2. Norm Stewart: Univ. of Missouri
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    ½ Jarvis ½ Georgetown
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Mike Jarvis - April Fools
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Mike Jarvis Promo Continuous Roll
  - Mike Jarvis Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 12/1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    GWU Radio Ads w/ Ken Beatrice 12/83
  - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    "Ted St. Martin Coors Light Sharpshooter" 1989/90
  - Miscellaneous, 09/1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Media Seminar GW 9-92 MBB
  - Miscellaneous, 09/1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Melissa Anne Boynton Cypress Creek High School Houston, Texas District Meet 1991, 1992 & 1993 (Diving)
  - Miscellaneous, 10/11/1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Men's and Women's Basketball '95-'96 Headshots Back up of Master Tapes 10/11/95
  - Miscellaneous, 12/14/1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    U.S. Women's Basketball 12/14/95
  - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    1998 Spring Sports © 1998 EMTV Channel 27 Production GWU Produced by Lauren Edwards Segments Produced by Crew-Joy Allen; M Tennis-Wendy Schwarn; Golf-Joel Crespo; W Tennis-Kim Richler; Baseball-Lauren Edwards
  - Miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    1999-2000 Always Kids Campaign Quarter 1 Spots & Documentary
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    All For One In The Spirit Of The Race (Men's Crew)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    A.U. Lady Eagles CAA - Highlights
  - Miscellaneous, 02/21/1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    "Bald Nite" Halftime Jarvis Look-alike Contest GW vs. WVU 2/21/92
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    B-Ball Tape (music)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    GW Women vs. SJU (ESPN) GW Men vs. JMU (ESPN)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Lifetime Television "Take A Girl To A Game"
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Men's Baseball
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    NBA/NHL Sampler
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    NABC History of Basketball
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Now I Get It? Recruitment Retention Endowment Teamline
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Something Happens Here The Movie
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Speaking Specialists Indiana State University (Football)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Sport news (local news not GW), Oprah Winfrey Show
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    SNL with Charles Barkley
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    SPC Chad Senior, Modern Pentathlete
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Specialist Chad Senior U.S. Army World Class Athlete Modern Pentathlon Olympic Qualifier
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    SFX
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Tentley Study Center "Keeping Their Dreams Supreme"
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    WCB Ga. Tech vs. VA ACC Finals
  - Unknown Sports, 11/22/1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    GW vs. Penn State 11/22/86
  - Unknown Sports, 12/14/1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    GW Head Trainer Dec 14 '90 Tape 1
  - Unknown Sports, 02/09/1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Pre Game Start 1st Half Feb 9 91 #3
  - Unknown Sports, 12/09/1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    12/9/93 Home Team Sports Intern Spot (Revised)
  - Unknown Sports, 09/12/1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    The V Foundation 3 Spots (:30) Date:9/12/95
  - Unknown Sports, 09/14/1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    G.W. vs. Georgetown 9/14/95
  - Unknown Sports, 09/14/1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    G.W. vs. Georgetown 9/14/95 Tape 2 of 3
  - Unknown Sports, 09/14/1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    G.W. vs. Georgetown 9/14/95 Tape 3 of 3
  - Unknown Sports, 02/24/1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Goin Deep Show 206 2/24/99
  - Unknown Sports, 01/19/2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Xavier @ George Washington 1/19/03 A 10 TV Tape 1 of 2
  - Unknown Sports, 01/19/2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Xavier @ George Washington 1/19/03 A 10 TV Tape 2 of 2
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    A 10 Training Promo GW
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Franklin National Bank Classic :30 Promo
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Gold in Phoe. Fligh Phoe. to Seattle Kingdome Practice
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    GW Footage Packages-VO's & SOT's
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    GW logo
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    George Washington/Stanford 11/30 Tape 1
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    George Washington/Stanford 11/30 Tape 2
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    G.W.U. Road to Sweet 16 Tape 1 Announcement, Leaving
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    G.W.U. Road to Sweet 16 Tape 2 Plane to Tuscon
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    G.W. University 2:30 minute spot
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    GW vs. URI 2nd Half
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    GW Voice Over for Highlight Tape GW Men Highlights Mixed
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Unlabeled 8mm Videocassette
  - Unknown Sports, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    George Washington University Women's Basketball Highlights 1997-98
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    GW Women's Basketball Hilites 1993-1994
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    1993 NCAA MBB Tourney GW vs. Southern/Michigan
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    "The George Washington University 1994-95 Basketball Team Season Highlights"
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    1995-96 George Washington Colonials Women's Basketball
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    1999-2000 George Washington Women's Basketball Highlights
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    1/29 GWU beats Xavier By Joyce Jackson and David Satchell
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/17/1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Fox 5 2/17/99 Shawnta Rogers Piece
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 03/07/1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Atlantic 10 Tournament Finals George Washington vs. Xavier (L) March 7, 1998
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Men's and Women's Basketball 2000-01 Highlight Video Garrett O'Donnell Comcast Sportsnet
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 05/07/2001 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Karl Hobbs Press Conference May 7, 2001
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Mike Brown WRC-Sports
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    91-92 MBB Highlights
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Wireless Mic-Mike Jarvis
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/27/1991-03/22/1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    The Mike Jarvis Show/Hts Feb. 27, March 5, 12, 22, 1991
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 12/07/1998 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Franklin National Bank Classic George Washington vs. Pennsylvania (W) December 7, 1998
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/14/1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    George Washington vs. UMASS February 14, 1995
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 01/15/1995 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    George Washington vs. UMASS 1/15/95 (T.V. Game)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/24/1996 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    George Washington vs. UMASS February 24, 1996
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/27/1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    MADD Sports #99-05 Air: 2/27/99 TRT: 27:50
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    MADD Sports #22 Val Brown
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/04/2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    GWU vs. Xavier (For 2/4/01 Sports Info)
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    GW NIT '94
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    Howard vs. A&T
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/21/1995 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Alexander Koul 2/21/95
  - Miscellaneous Athletic Tapes, 02/02/2001 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    GW vs. Dayton 2/2/01 TV Copy (Sports Info Copy)
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 12/06/2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    BBandT 12/6/03 Part 1 tape 1 of 2
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 12/06/2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    BBandT 12/6/03 Part 2 tape 1 of 2
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 12/06/2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    BBandT 12/6/03 Tape 2 of 2
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 12/07/2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    BB&T Classic - Tape 2 of 3 12/7/03
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 12/07/2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    BB&T Classic - Tape 3 of 3 12/7/03
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    LAS @ GW 1st Half 1/17
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    LAS @ GW 2nd Half 1/17
  - Miscellaneous Sports Beta Tapes, 03/25/2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    2003 WNCAA Tournament GW vs. NOVA-2nd Round 3/25/03 GW vs. Oklahoma-1st Round 3/23
  - Academics and Athletics, 11/05/1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Athletics: A Catalyst For Change, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    This videotape was developed by the NCAA Council Subcommittee to Review Minority Opportunities in Intercollegiate Athletics in an effort to provide a historical view of minorities' participation in athletics, with an emphasis on administrative achievements. Additionally, this videotape was developed to promote the NCAA Ethnic Minority Enchancement Program.
  - GW vs. Temple and GW vs. ODU, 01/10/1991-01/14/1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - George Washington vs. Loyola Game Tape, 11/27/1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - GW Soccer, 09/19/1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MJ Shows 1-7, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - GW Women's Basketball Highlights, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - George Washington's Men's Basketball 1992-1993, Road to the Sweet Sixteen (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - GW Women's Basketball Hilites, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - GW Men's Basketball Hilites, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GW Men's Basketball Hilites, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - George Washington Colonials Women's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - George Washington University Women's Basketball Highlights, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - George Washington Women's Basketball Highlights, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - George Washington Women's Basketball Highlight Video, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Baseball, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Geroge Washington Women's Basketball Highlights, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - George Washington 2002-2003 Women's Basketball Highlight Tape (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - George Washington University Basketball Video Yearbook 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Four Athletes, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Produced by Liz Claiborne, Incs.'s Women's Work Program, Northeastern University's Center for the Study of Sport in Society, and the College Football Association. Featuring Matt Russell, Chad Johnston, Paul Beckwith, and James Hamilton.
  - Project Teamwork, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    VHS. Videos 1 and 2. Produced for the Northeastern University's Center for the Study of Sport in Society.
  - Mike J. tape from Reston, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - BB&T Classic Melt Reel, Maryland vs. Kansas, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Betacam SP
  - Childhelp, 03/05/1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Public Service Announcement. Audio Master with low res pix.
  - UConn Basketball 2000-2001 Highlight Tape (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - BB&T Classic, UMass vs. Maryland, 12/02/1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Reel 1 of 2.
  - BB&T Classic, U Mass vs. Maryland, 12/02/1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Reel 2 of 2.
  - Childhelp, 09/03/1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Summer Productions, Childhelp
  - BB&T Classic, California vs. Maryland, 12/08/1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Reel 1 of 2
  - BB&T Classic, California vs. Maryland, 12/08/1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Reel 2 of 2
  - BBT Classic, MCI Center, Illinois vs. Maryland, 12/04/1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Tape 1 of 2
  - BBT Classic, MCI Center, Illinois vs. Maryland, 12/04/1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Tape 2 of 2
  - Michigan Highlights, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Basketball?
  - Maryland Basketball Metts vs. Illinois, George Washington University, and George Mason, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - GWU Hilites '77, 05/20/1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    16mm film. J.R. Black
  - 18mm film, Women's Athletics, 1973; RG0054 Series 38 (Box SERIES 38 BOX 16, Reel 1)
  - 18mm film, Women in Sports: An Informal History, 1979; RG0054 Series 38 (Box SERIES 38 BOX 17, Reel 1)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Seton Hall, Game 1 (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 1)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Seton Hall, Game 1 (Betacam), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 2)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Seton Hall, Game 1 (Betacam), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 3)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Seton Hall (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 4)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Seton Hall, In-Arena (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 5)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Maryland (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 6)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Maryland, In-Arena (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 7)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Maryland (VHS), 12/04/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 8)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Seton Hall (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 9)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Seton Hall (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 10)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Seton Hall (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 11)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Seton Hall, In-Arena (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 12)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Illinois vs. Seton Hall, Tape 2 (Betacam), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 13)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland, Tape 3 (Betacam), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 14)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland, In-Arena (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 15)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland, In-Arena (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 16)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland, In-Arena (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 17)